Guide to the Clifford K. Berryman cartoon collection, 1899-1949 MS2024
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- No title, Circa 1945 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  shows Uncle Sam hoisting the flags "V-E Day" and "V-J Day" up a flagpole, amid graveyard crosses marked "Midway," "Iwo Jima," and others; teddy bear is holding an olive branch, and Truman comments "And This Time We Are Going To Win The Peace, Too!"
- No title, 1945 August 23 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  shows DeGaulle, Attlee, Stalin and Chiang Kai-Shek with fire hoses plugged into a hydrant marked "Lend Lease"; Truman is turning a wrench on the hydrant
- No title, 1945 October (Box 6, Folder 19)
  shows John Q. Public sitting on the steps of the Supreme Court looking a headline that reads "French Vote To Change Constitution". He wonders why "They Went To All That Trouble"
- No title, undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
  shows Schwellenbach asking Frances Perkins "What's He Got That We Haven't Got?" as he holds up the headline "Movie Industry Offers Krug $75,000 A Year As Labor Director"
- "Just Practicing", Circa 1946 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  shows Brewster, Ferguson, George and Barkley at the "Pearl Harbor Investigation" throwing books at each other
- No title, 1946 January 14 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  shows GI's overseas exclaiming "I Want To Come Home"; John Q. Public standing on the North American continent, asks "Why?" as strikes burst like bombs around him
- No title, 1946 March 11 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  shows Truman showing John Q. Public various military-related headlines. John Q. Public is scratching his head, saying "It's Hard For Me To See How They Add Up"
- "The House of Representatives Resumes Its Pre-Pearl Harbor Position", 1946 April 22 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  shows man with his head stuck like an ostrich in the sand
- "The Great Rocket Bomb Experiment", 1946 June 17 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  shows John Q. Citizen strapped to a rocket "Uncontrolled Prices". "Congress" assures him that "The Laws Of Gravity" will bring him back
- No title, 1946 June 30 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  shows unidentified figure plugging his ears as a war plane and ships loom on the horizon
- No title, 1946 July 02 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  shows Forrestal overlooking destroyed Naval ships, commenting "Flash This Signal Around The World: They Didn't Get The Navy's Goat"
- No title, 1946 July 06 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  shows Truman and unidentified figure with microphones, arguing. Barkley is sitting in between them, holding a large sack "Price Controls" and asking "But Who Is It Always Left Holding The Bag"
- No title, 1946 July 11 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  shows a rocket marked "This Rocket Climbed 83 Miles For A New Record" crashing to earth. John Q. Public, holding the tail of the "Food Prices" rocket says, "But Watch Me, Brother"
- No title, 1946 October 08 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  shows John Q. Voter laughing with the GOP elephant as Hannegan asks "What's Funny...?"
- "1492-Columbus Day-1946", 1946 October 12 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  shows Uncle Sam dismayed at all the "Gimme's" bursting around him. Christopher Columbus is climbing up the Washington Monument, saying "I Sure Started Something When I Discovered America."
- No title, 1946 November 21 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  shows Mason, Young, and Grant denying responsibility for the "Slum Reclamation Project"; George Washington urges them on, saying "...You've Got A Big Job To Do"
- "No Aid To Digestion", 1946 November 28 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  shows Dewey, Taft, Reece, Bricker, Martin, White, and Vandenburg dining over the turkey "November Elections" as John Q. Public asks "Hey! When Do I Get Paid For The Turkey?"
- No title, 1947 January 30 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  shows Langer wielding a hatchet and dancing around the "Indian Bureau", a Native American figure which is tied to a pole
- No title, 1947 February 09 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  shows Hannegan and Reece as hens in the "1948 Presidential Candidate Hatchery"
- No title, 1947 February 25 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  shows John Q. Public outside on a cold day, holding a headline which reads "Admiral Byrd Heads Homeward To Escape Antarctic Ice Belt". Public comments that Byrd is "...Jumping From The Frying Pan Into The Fire"
- No title, 1947 February 27 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  shows "Congress" with a shotgun "Labor Legislation" at a church with the bridal couple Green and Murray. Green tells Murray "No! Phil, Let Him Shoot"
- No title, 1947 March 04 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  shows Dewey awakened to find the screaming orphan "New York Teachers' Unrest" on his doorstep
- No title, 1947 March 20 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  shows game warden Vandenberg blocking poacher Gael Sullivan, who is hoping to bag politicians into the "Democratic National Committee". The area is "Preserved For A Bi-partisan Foreign Relations Policy"
- "Advice from An Expert In Internal Affairs", 1947 April 09 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  shows Gromyko chiding Uncle Sam that he is "Interfering In The Internal Affairs Of Greece And Turkey"; behind Gromyko is a bear with a Russian cap; clothing marked "Finland" "Hungary" and etc., strewn about
- No title, 1947 April 13 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  shows John Bull sitting perturbed in a chair as Wallace speaks at a BBC microphone. Bull muses "The War-The Blitz-Empire Liquidation-Blizzards-Famine-Floods-And Now Henry Wallace"
- No title, 1947 May 01 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  shows a farmer "House Appropriations Committee" tending the field "Voice Of America" instead of the overgrown "Waste" and "Extravagance". Uncle Sam asks him "Hey, Aren't You In The Wrong Patch?"
- "It's Going To Be The Most Exciting Thing Since Ben Hur", 1947 May 06 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  shows charioteers Taft and Martin riding the "Republican Legislative Program" and whipping the elephant GOP. They are on a treadmill, trying to reach "July Adjournment"
- No title, 1947 May 07 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  shows Stassen holding up a sign "The Voice Of Stalin As Relayed By Me"; in the background is Stalin, leaning back in a chair, saying "Cooperation? It's Wonderful!" and Taber gagging the mouth of Uncle Sam who is the "Voice of America."
- "Too Many Broths May Spoil the Cook", 1947 May 22 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  shows "Congress" trying to fit the pot "Health Insurance" on a stove already filled with "Voice Of America," "Labor Bill", "Tax Reduction", and other pots
- No title, 1947 June 17 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  shows Truman tripping an elephant "GOP" whose egg basket "Tax Reduction" spills over; "You'll Be Sorry!" says the GOP
- "Maybe They Are Somebody's Pipe Dreams", 1947 July 08 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  shows Stalin blowing rings of smoke around Uncle Sam
- "Who Said Marathon Racing Was A Dull Sport?", 1947 July 15 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  shows "Tax Reduction Bill" running back and forth between Congress and the White House, as John Q. Public watches from bleacher seats
- No title, 1947 July 17 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  shows Warren and Dewey at the "Conference of Governors"; Warren asks Dewey "Do You Find It Hard To Keep Your Mind On Gubernatorial Problems These Days?"; Dewey responds, "There Are Some Distractions"
- "Now We Can Share Our Blessings With The World", 1947 July 27 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  shows Congress amid a congestion of airplanes, buses, cars, and people, all running away from the Capitol building
- No title, 1947 August 13 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  shows William Green, president of the AFL-CIO putting up a sign "Labor Will Defeat Taft If Picked By GOP." Dewey and Taft, behind Green, remark "Don't Start Counting Chickens Tom, He'll Try Just As Hard To Defeat You"
- "Handing Over 'The White Man's Burden'", 1947 August 15 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  shows Mountbatten giving the country of India to Jinnah and Nehru
- No title, 1947 August 24 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  shows "What Was Forecast" (the Taft-Hartley Bill driving Murray, Lewis, and Green with whips and chains) and "What Seems To Have Happened" (Murray, Lewis, and Green driving the Taft-Hartley bill)
- "Rude Interruption", 1947 August 26 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  shows Ecuador shooting off pistols outside the "Inter-American Defense Conference"
- No title, 1947 October 05 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  shows "Ohio Mother of Presidents" welcoming back Taft, who has come from "The West" and left a trail of "Speeches," behind him; She asks "But Bob, Where Are The Delegates?"
- No title, but on back is "Now What Would You Do About Something That Hasn't Been Offered", 1947 October 19 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  shows Eisenhower at a desk, surrounded by many offers for the presidency; He comments "The Trouble Is That The People Who Offer Me These Things Do Not Own What They Offer"
- "You Can See Who's Running. But Who Is Ahead?", 1947 November 16 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  shows Stassen, Dewey, Warren and Taft on the "1948 Track." Though they are tied in the race, Dewey and Warren are simply standing still, while Stassen and Taft are running
- No title, 1947 November 18 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  shows the orphans of "Price Control", "Aid To Europe", and "Wage Control" left on the steps of "Congress" "Compliments Of H.S. Truman"
- "Well, They Got Their Isolation", 1947 December 03 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  shows McKellar, O'Daniel, Taylor, Langer, Moore and Robertson on a raft in the ocean; a flag on the raft says "Senate Opposition To Foreign Aid"
- No title, 1947 December 21 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  shows Anderson dressed as Santa Claus, stuffing papers into a sack marked "14000 Names Of Big Speculators"; He comments "Looks Like Somebody Is Going To Get A Christmas Present"
- "Bringing Up The Artillery", 1948 January 06 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  shows Truman pointing the cannons "State Of The Union" "Economic Report" and "Budget Message" at the Capitol building
- "A Little Privacy For The President", 1948 January 08 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  shows a crowd of people at the White House fence, staring at Truman inside
- "But Doesn't Anybody Ever Come Out?", 1948 February 29 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  shows a boy "Finland" being shown into an examination room by doctor Stalin; The caps of "Lithuania" "Czechoslovakia" and other bloc countries hang by the door
- "'He Travels The Fastest Who Travels Alone'", 1948 March 13 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  shows the knight "European Recovery Program" being followed by Martin, Halleck and Eaton, who hold up riders "Military Aid To China" "Military Aids To Greece" and "Military Aid To Turkey" respectively
- "Heralds of Spring", 1948 March 16 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  shows the "First Robin" and Lewis putting up a sign "The Miners Will Work When Willing And Able And They're Not Too Willing"; John Q. Public looks on and comments "I Guess That Makes It Unanimous"
- "Some of Yesteryear's Rabbits Are Busy Again", 1948 March 28 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  shows unidentified figure in academic gown being chased by rabbits holding signs which read "Ike"
- No title, 1948 April 08 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  shows Dewey leaving the state of Wisconsin; he tells Stassen and unidentified figure, who are carrying sacks of "Delegates" that he "Hopes He, Shall Return"
- No title, 1948 April 29 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  shows Mason, Gen Young and Russ Young examining "D.C." with a "Loyalty Probe"; they remark, "He Looks Harmless Enough But You Never Can Tell"
- No title, 1948 July 18 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  shows a donkey and a "Southern Democrat" holding a baby "State's Rights" sitting on a tree limb; Swirling under them is the river "GOP"
- "Decorations Of The Iron Curtain In Honor Of United Nations Week", 1948 October 27 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  shows Vishinsky painting "NO" on each sheet of the wall
- "Why Not Have A Lifelike Float In The Parade?", 1948 December 21 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  shows "Congress" holding "DC" upside-down by the ankles on a float marked "District of Columbia"; As "D.C."'s money falls out of his pockets, three unidentified figures collect it in their hats. Teddy bear carries a flag reading "Taxation Without Representation"
- "Squash Center Comment On National Defense", 1949 October 09 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  shows ten country men talking about the upcoming election, lobbyists, the navy, and other topics
- No title, undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
  shows a goat "Independent Party" holding the coattails of the elephant "G.O.P."; they pass a "News Bulletin" reading "New Liberal Party Proposed At Banquet In New York- To Be Recruited From Liberal Thinkers In Both Old Political Parties"; "Independent Party" comments "It's A Fine Idea.." "But To Hold On To Sure Bread And Butter"
- "The Pinchot-Davis Contribution Contest", undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
  shows two unidentified figures bidding their "Bonds" "Salary" and "Dividends" as "Unemployment" asks "How About A Little Something On My Account?"
- "Better Keep Your Eyes Behind You, Harold!", Circa 1935 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  shows Harold Ickes shouting "Beware Of Those Sixty Families" into a microphone, as a person "C.C.C." rakes "$8400000" in leaves behind him
- "A Reverse Version of Cant 00' Talk?", undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
  shows "Mayor Hylan" dressed in baby clothes; opposite him is a tiger labeled "Tam." which asks him, "Are You Goin' To Bolt?"
- No title, Circa 1929 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  shows Hoover pointing to his ear, as crowds of "Eastern Delegation", "Northern Delegation", and other job seekers wait outside; an "Ear Specialist" tells Hoover "It's Nothing Serious! Simply Ear Fatigue Resulting From An Ear Full!"
- "The Boy Stood On The Burning Deck While Eliza Crossed The Ice!", undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
  shows Dave Dubinsky with the "Garment Baby" running cross ice and Charlie Howard diving overboard; John Lewis and the "CIO" are left on deck
- No title, undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
  shows Franklin D. Roosevelt appealing to the Goose "U.S. Business"; Roosevelt says "It's All Right To Lay Golden Eggs But You Watch Your Step"; legions of farmers with their hoes march in the foreground
- No title, undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
  shows Petrillo with a fiddle sitting outside the window of Congress; Congress throws a shoe tagged "House Votes Petrillo Curb 222 to 43"; Petrillo remarks "I Guess I Must Have Hit A Sour Note"
- "Heroes Of The North", undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
  shows unidentified figure with sled dogs; penciled in is "Rich'd Byrd"
- No title, undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
  shows Lewis, Franklin D. Roosevelt, and LaFollette embracing on a couch; Farley is standing with his hat and bag and remarks "Just One Happy Family. Yeah, I Think It's Time To Go Now!"
- No title, undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
  shows Fess reading the headline "Man Bests Lion In Fight By Seizing Its Tongue"; meanwhile, a donkey is outside calling for a "Four Year Moratorium For The G.O.P", "Down With The Drought", etc; Fess muses "Wish I Could Get Hold Of That Jackass's Tongue!"
- No title, undated (Box 9, Folder 12)
  shows Chairman Hawley trying to golf in the "Tariff Revision Golf Links"; he comments "Nothing' But Rough! All The Fairways Seem To Have Been Removed!"
- "The Unsuccessful Hypnotist", Circa 1930 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  shows Dr. Brookhard trying to hypnotize Herbert Hoover, but Hoover responds "No, I Can't See Any Debenture Delights"; Frazier, looking on, grumbles, "I Also Thought He'd Be Easy"
- "Herbert Hoover Hay!", Circa 1933 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  shows farmer Herbert Hoover feeding the GOP hay "Back To The Constitution"; A Progressive goat is eating "New Deal Scraps"; The GOP tells him "Anyhow, It's Better'n You've Been Getting Lately!"
- "This Endeth Linevitch's Lesson", undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
  shows Linevitch being stopped from carving up a plate of "Oyama" men by Witte and a "Peace Agreement"
- No title, undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
  shows Fiorello LaGuardia holding loaves of bread as the "Director General UNRRA"; an emaciated tiger "Tammany" comments "I Hope He Does Better By Them Than He Did For Me"
- No title, Circa 1928 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  shows elderly woman commenting "Cal Thinks Well Of The David Family Anyhow!"; on the floor is a headline reading "The Are Now Two Cabinet Members Named Davis"
- No title, Circa 1939 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  shows Franklin D. Roosevelt dressed as blind justice, weighing "Jackson" and "Douglas"; teddy bear tells him, "Better Take That Blindfold Off, Mr. President!"
- "The Good Story", Circa 1930 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  shows unidentified figure and a tiger (representing Tammany Hall?) laughing at a picture of Franklin D. Roosevelt, "Our Governor," on the wall
- No title, undated (Box 9, Folder 20)
  shows "Congress" looking at a painting of a grand building "President's Proposal To Reorganize Government Housing Agencies"; "John Q. Taxpaper" points to a shack "Our Housing Mess" and asks, "..What Are We Going To Do About This?"
- No title, undated (Box 9, Folder 21)
  shows bricklayers "Labor" and "Capital" laying progressively larger bricks of "Prices" and "Wage Increase"; They comment "Maybe We Ought To Stop Now Before It Falls Over!"
- "Poor Old Jim Toppled Over", undated (Box 9, Folder 22)
  shows soldiers in a trench
- No title, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
  shows eagle sitting on the back of a chair marked "NRA" amid a sledgehammer, "code book," and rubble. An unidentified figure is walking into the sunset
- "The New Western Front!", Circa 1939 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  shows the Capitol smoking with the "Neutrality Debate" as Daladier, Chamberlain, Stalin and others on the "Western Front" look on
- No title, Circa 1940 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  shows Molotov with "Estonia" "Slice of Poland" "Latvia" "Lithuania" and "Russian-German Treaty" in his vest pockets. He asks Franklin D. Roosevelt, "What Do You Mean, Sending Me A Letter About Finland? Why You Don't Act Like A Neutral! Look At Me!"
- "The Uninvited Delegate", Circa 1945 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  shows "Polish Issue" sitting down at the "United Nations Conference" table with Eden, Molotov, and Stettinus
- "Obscuring The View! (With No Apologies To Unsightly Signs)", undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
  shows a group of roadside advertisements, "Muscle Shoals Measure," "Abolishment Of Lame Duck Sessions," etc. The horizon is marked "No Extra Session"
- "How's That?", undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
  shows automobiles attached to floating blimps marked "D.C. Parking Service"
- "'Windfall Taxation'- New Name But Same Old Sensation!", Circa 1935 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  shows Wallace, Ickes, Tugwell, and Hopkins in an apple tree. An apple "Increased Taxes", drops on the head of "Tax-Payer" who cries "You Can't Tell Me The Wind's Doin' That!"
- "Teaching The Young Idea How To Shoot (And He Wants To Take Right Hold)" also "1754 Erie St., N.W., Born June 8th 1902 James T. (Heavy) Weight 12 Pounds", undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
  shows unidentified figure (probably Berryman) with a baby, showing the baby an autographed portrait of James L. Norris "For National Committeeman"
- No title, undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
  shows Blease, Heflin, Simmons, and Ransdell eyeing "America's Cup"; they remark "We Know Just How Sir Thomas Feels!"
- No title, undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
  shows tourist and Uncle Sam surrounded by roadside billboards for tires, Carrotine, "The Peoples Candidate John Smith" and others. Uncle Sam wears a placard reading "See America First"
- "Outside Voices" also "Yell, Fellers, Yell! The Chairman Of The Platform Committee Is Reading The Statehood Plank", Circa 1908 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  shows "Oklahoma" "Arizona" and "New Mexico" laughing outside of the tent "G.O.P. National Convention Chicago"
- "Interested Readers", Circa 1908 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  shows several politicos by a train track reading literature left by the "Taft Presidential Special"
- No title, undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
  shows elderly woman "Democracy" looking at rolls of wallpaper marked "States Rights" "Populism" "Recall Of Judges" and others; she comments "Lan' Sakes! I'm Tempted To Paper Every Room With Those Precious Designs"
- No title, Circa 1940 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  shows large bear "U.S.S.R" pointing at a small man "Finland" and crying to Stalin "Please Make That Great Big Bully Stop Picking On Me!"
- No title, undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
  shows H.A. Wallace courting LaFollette; a frustrated "Wisconsin Democracy" stomps off, commenting "Lan' Sakes! You Can Never Guess These Hop-Around Boys!"
- No title, undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
  shows "Jimmy Big Heart Chief Of The Navajos" in Native American dress and brandishing a tomahawk with a heart-shaped blade "Mayor Walker"; "New York" comments "I Knew If You Kept Actin' Like A Wild Indian Somethin' Would Happen To You"
- No title, undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
  shows Gene Tunney reading various headlines about fist fights in Congress; he muses "I've Been Thinking All Along That The Rules Committee Should Handle These Affairs"
- No title, undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
  shows "Mayor Walker" with the placard "We Are Determined To Maintain The Reputation Justly Won Many Years Back As Being The Cleanest, Most Moral City In The World"; behind him is the Tammany tiger, holding a lily, and leaning on Walker, saying "My Jimmy Boy!"
- "Transmission Delayed By Strike", undated (Box 11, Folder 13)
  shows cobwebbed telegraph and telegram from "John Q. Citizen" reading "Uncle Sam, Washington D.C. What has become of the theory that we have a government of the people, by the people, for the people?"
- No title, undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
  shows Congress napping in a rocking chair beside a falling-down shack "U.S.A."; Truman complains to Uncle Sam and teddy bear "I Wish You'd Speak To Him, Uncle. He'll Do Anything To Please The Neighbors But I Can't Get Him To Do A Thing Around The House"
- No title, Circa 1918 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  shows various politicians climbing onto the bandwagon "Votes For Women" at the "Last Call"
- No title, undated (Box 11, Folder 16)
  shows Uncle Sam at a "U.S. Railway Mail" train taking off his jacket; he decides, "Reckon It's Up To Me To Be A Strike Breaker"
- No title, Circa 1947 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  shows "D.C." shackled to the ball "Taxation Without Representation" and Truman trying to saw at the chain; "D.C." points to "Congress," which is holding the key "Sumners Capper Amendment"
- No title, Circa 1905 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  facsimile, shows Theodore Roosevelt presiding "Dee-Lighted" over the "Canal Route" and teddy bear looking through his binoculars
- "Rosalind Amongst The Vice Presidential Timber", undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
  shows Cannon in Shakespearean garb amid trees marked "Cannon"
- "Expensive Echoes", Circa 1925 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  shows Calvin Coolidge looking at lengthy sections of the Congressional Record; he remarks "Not A Thought Of My Economy Policy"
- "The President Recently Dug Worms For Fishing", Circa 1925 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  shows Calvin Coolidge putting worms "Tax Reduction" and "Economy" in a can; "This Ought To Catch A Big Bunch" he remarks
- "Thus Endeth The 71st", Circa 1931 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  shows Herbert Hoover and Congress leaning back to back, exhausted, with a dismantled Capitol in the background. On verso is a partial sketch of "Miss Democracy," a dog and an unidentified figure
- "Upholstering Bills Could Have Been Saved", Circa 1895 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  shows a rotund Grover Cleveland in a Shakepearean costume, arm in arm with S.C. Lemly and Shatter, on the way "To The Coronation"
- "A Southwestern Soliloquy", undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
  shows Burleson looking at the "Post Office News" that "Three Letter Mailed To Ollie James From Kentucky on March 6 1914 Have Just Been Delivered"; Burleson comments "So That's The New Service They Promised"
- No title, Circa 1934 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  shows Voorhis, Pepper, Hillman, Biddle, Black and Michelson at the "Political Front" at "Fort New Deal"
- "A Word To The Wise", undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
  shows Blum, Daladier, Reynaud, an unidentified figure, and Baldwin sitting on the "Has Been" bench; they tell Rayburn, Bankhead, Barkley and Minton "If We Had It To Do Over Again, Boys, We Wouldn't Even Talk Of Adjournment"
- "The 'Numbers' Is Such A Harmless Little Game", undated (Box 12, Folder 11)